{
    "applicationTitle": "Riddle Me This",
    "questionary": [
    {
        "question": "How old is Guido?",
        "attempts": 5,
        "answers": ["3", "44", "30", "41", "50", "28"],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
        "correctAnswerValue": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "How old is Miro?",
        "attempts": 3,
        "answers": ["3", "44", "30", "41", "50", "28"],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 3,
        "correctAnswerValue": "41"
    },
    {
        "question": "Guido original contry is?",
        "attempts": 5,
        "answers": ["France", "Germany", "Cuba", "Canada", "Brazil", "USA"],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
        "correctAnswerValue": "Cuba"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where was Miro born?",
        "attempts": 4,
        "answers": ["Slovakia", "Germany", "Cuba", "Canada", "Brazil", "USA"],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
        "correctAnswerValue": "Slovakia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where does Miro live?",
        "attempts": 5,
        "answers": ["Rio", "Manchester", "Tokyo", "New York", "Berlin", "Barcelona"],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
        "correctAnswerValue": "Manchester"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where Miro run his first maratthon?",
        "attempts": 5,
        "answers": ["Barcelona", "Rio", "Tokio", "Paris", "Kosice", "Gelnica"],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 0,
        "correctAnswerValue": "Barcelona"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many bikes does have Miro?",
        "attempts": 5,
        "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "3", "4", "5"],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 2,
        "correctAnswerValue": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Slovak number styri is in English language?",
        "attempts": 5,
        "answers": ["2", "4", "6", "8", "10", "12"],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 1,
        "correctAnswerValue": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where was Miro living for 3 months in America?",
        "attempts": 5,
        "answers": ["New York", "Washinghton", "Chicago", "Denver", "Raleigh", "San Francisco"],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 4,
        "correctAnswerValue": "Raleigh"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the most famous Slovak hero?"
        "attempts": 5,
        "answers": ["Miro", "Palo", "Fero", "Tibike", "Janko Hrasko", "Jurko Janosik"],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 5,
        "correctAnswerValue": "Jurko Janosik"
    }
    ]
}


























